- [thunderclap]
- [banner fluttering]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[growls]
[grunts]
[scoffs]
[MAN] The Heavy Knight.
A densely armored class
that specializes in defense
and draws enemy attacks
to protect allies.
But, compared to the many
other defensive classes,
it lacks versatility.
With its weak
offensive abilities,
leveling up
is almost impossible.
As a result...
...it's considered to be
a truly unfortunate
and defective class.
[girl chuckles]
[chuckles]
[♪ opening theme song playing]
[thunder cracks]
[boy panting]
[grunts]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[MAN]
Regardless of what it might be,
every time I've learned
- or seen something here...
- Huh?
- [footsteps approaching]
- Huh.
[grunts, gasps]
[MAN]...I've always had
this inexplicable feeling
that I already knew what it was.
[BOY] Somehow, it seems like
I've seen all of this before.
Huh?
[gasps]
[whooshing]
[MAN 1] Huh?
- [spider screeches]
- [man 1 grunts]
[♪ rock music playing]
- [man 2 grunts]
- [sword slashes]
- [monster growls]
- [grunts]
- [monster roars]
- [yells]
- [spider screeches]
- [man 2 grunting]
[grunts]
[yells]
[grunting]
[panting]
[chuckles]
[GIRL] Doppellusion!
[woman laughs]
Time to show you what a true
Master Swordsman can do!
[grunts] Cold-As-Steel Cutter!
- [woman grunts]
- [man 2 strains]
- [both grunting]
- [swords clashing]
[grunting]
- [both grunts]
- [swords clash]
[both grunts]
- [laughs smugly]
- [man 1 grunts]
- [woman laughs evilly]
- [gasps]
[yells]
- [monster growls]
- [grunts]
- [sword slashes]
[man 3 yells]
[monster groans]
[grunts]
[spider screeches]
- [man 1 screams fiercely]
- [man 2 grunts]
[MAN] And today...
as heir to the Edvaughn family,
I'm about to undertake
the Ritual of Divine Blessing.
[crowd murmuring]
There's that peculiar feeling
of déjàà vu again.
It's all right, my son.
You must have faith.
Trust in the God of the Sword.
♪
[breathes shakily]
[sighs]
Now, Elymas Edvaughn...
I grant you the divine blessing
of a class.
Mm. Baptisma!
[ELYMAS] I've seen this.
Was it five years ago?
No, before that.
Long before I'd even been born.
[gasps]
I was addicted
to an online VR game
called Magic World,
and played it obsessively.
[gasps]
Yet the world I'm in now
is exactly like it!
It's hard to believe,
but I've been reincarnated.
With everything I know
about the game,
I'm guaranteed
to be a success here.
[grunts]
And with this advantage,
I hope I'm put
into my favorite class.
The broken one that's said
to be the strongest
in all of Magic World.
[gasps]
[ELYMAS] All right!
[gasps happily]
I'm a Heavy Knight, Father.
I did it!
[Elymas's father gasps]
You're-- You're what?!
- Father?
- [crowd chattering]
My son? No!
You are a Master Swordsman, right?
[Elymas gasps]
- [crowd whispering]
- [gasps]
[splutters]
[Elymas gasps] My past
and present memories
have been mixed up!
In this world,
simple and powerful classes
are widely celebrated.
But those that take time
are sold short.
Their analysis
and testing of classes
must be severely
lagging behind.
- [ELYMAS] Uh, actually, I--
- [woman gasps]
[ELYMAS'S FATHER] Show me!
[gasps]
So it is true!
- How could this be?
- [gasps]
With such low stats
and no decent attacking skills,
being a Heavy Knight
is utterly worthless!
Everyone knows it's a pitiful,
- defective class!
- But that simply isn't true!
They have the highest HP
and Defense, Father.
That's irrelevant,
just as you are!
- [grunts]
- [crowd gasps]
- [crowd chattering]
- [MAN] Oh!
[gasps]
- [Elymas groaning]
- [spits]
I'm glad it was here.
If we'd been shamed like this
out in public,
the Edvaughn name
would be ruined.
[groans]
- [gasps]
- [footsteps approaching]
[all gasp]
[♪ ethereal music playing]
- [Elymas's father gasps]
- [crowd whispering]
[WOMAN 1] Look at her.
[WOMAN 2]
She looks so beautiful now.
- [MAN 1] Who's that?
- [MAN 2] So lovely.
[MAN 3] The daughter
of a branch family?
- [MAN 4] Do you have any idea?
- [MAN 3] Are you certain?
[whispers continue]
[gasps]
[WOMAN] I'm supposed
to go through
the Ritual of Divine Blessing
as well.
May I do so?
[WOMAN 3] Someone like this
ought to know her place.
[ELYMAS] She's the daughter
of an Edvaughn branch family,
and her name is Malice.
We played together a few times
as children,
- but because of her status...
- [MAN 5] She's grown up.
...we've hardly spoken at all
these last five years.
[PRIEST] Uh,
but I couldn't possibly!
[ELYMAS'S FATHER]
I will allow it.
You may begin the ritual.
[MALICE] Mm.
[ELYMAS]
Something feels off about this.
Mm. Baptisma!
[ELYMAS'S FATHER] Hmm.
[sighs]
[MALICE] Hmm?
So, I'm a Master Swordsman, huh?
[crowd whispering]
[sighs]
Hmm.
I'm sorry.
But regrettably,
it seems I'm the one
who's taken all the skill.
[ELYMAS]
My bad feelings were justified.
A branch family's daughter
acquiring
the Master Swordsman class
could worsen
my father's terrible mood.
[thunder rumbling]
[gasps in shock, laughs]
[ELYMAS'S FATHER]
How wonderful, Malice!
I always knew
you were a true Edvaughn.
As of this very moment,
- you are officially my daughter.
- [gasps]
And you will be my heir.
[gasps sharply]
[MAN 6] He actually named
a branch family girl
as his heir?
[MAN 7]
It isn't without precedent.
[crowd whispering]
Father, I always thought
Lord Elymas-- No.
That Elymas could never bear
the burden
of being your true heir.
- [laughs evilly]
- [gasps]
[ELYMAS'S FATHER]
Begone, Elymas.
A disappointment like you
must never call himself my son!
- [Elymas gasps]
- As a Heavy Knight,
you've sullied
the Edvaughn family name!
- So leave this mansion at once!
- [gasps]
[gasps]
[crowds chattering]
[WOMAN 4] He's adopting
a branch family girl?
- [Elymas gasps]
- [MAN 8] I suppose
it can't be helped
at this point.
[WOMAN 5] He made a wise choice.
Surely you don't mean that,
Father!
Heavy Knights are powerful.
I-I swear. I'll bring honor to--
- [ELYMAS'S FATHER] Silence!
- [winces]
You're getting exactly
what you deserve.
Don't show your face here again.
- [gasps]
- If you ever use
the Edvaughn family name
outside of these walls,
I'll have your head
for such insolence!
[chuckles maliciously]
[gasps]
- [scoffs]
- [ELYMAS] Father!
[gasps]
[Malice chuckles softly]
[ELYMAS'S FATHER] Clean this up.
[chuckles]
[gasps in disbelief]
[thunder crashing]
[ELYMAS] No matter how much
I pleaded with him,
my father refused to listen.
- [BUTLER] Be safe out there.
- I was given a small bag
- with a few coins...
- Thank you.
...then left
after being kicked out
of the mansion that day.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[thunder cracks]
[♪ bright music playing]
[crowd chattering at distance]
[SOLDIER] Should we recruit
party members too?
Anybody will do,
as long as they're fast.
[indistinct chatter]
[chuckles softly]
[MAN 1] So, how have you been?
[MAN IN RED] Well, actually,
I'm planning to take on
- a promotion quest soon.
- [all gasp]
I've got some pull
with the examiners.
- [MAN 2] Wow!
- Lord Teal's amazing!
[giggles]
Today's the day, you two!
I'm ready to do my best!
- Whoop! Yeah!
- [man sighs]
Just try not to get in the way
this time.
- [girl groans]
- I wish at least once
- you would just hunt normally.
- [woman sighs]
[yawns]
[whimpers]
[sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
[WOMAN 1] My husband's fine
in public,
but at home, he's so simple.
[WOMAN 2] That's just men.
I mean,
what were you expecting?
[birds chirping]
[ELYMAS] My piece-of-shit father
put me through hell.
I lost my family, home,
and the life I knew.
But...
I've still got
the strongest class,
Heavy Knight!
That said,
the history of this world?
Even Rondalm, the city's name.
They're different
from the game I played.
Which means
I'll need to do some research.
First,
I'll test my class and skills.
Display stats.
If everything's been changed
and Heavy Knights aren't
as overpowered as they were,
then I'm screwed.
[gasps]
Great. Still good.
The skill tree.
This is what lets people choose
which types of skills they want
for a given situation.
At the moment,
I only have five skill points.
These are the bonus ones
you receive
after gaining your class.
After that, you gain one
per level as you advance.
It's no exaggeration to say
how they're assigned
can determine your fate.
There are two types of skills.
Those determined by class
are Fixed Skills,
and some are randomly assigned
at the start.
Oath of the Heavy Armor
is the only fixed class
skill tree.
[onlookers laughing]
Of all the ones
given to Heavy Knights,
people often refer to it
as the weakest and least useful.
Although it can be
fairly strong,
it isn't easy to use,
and many of its skills
have very limited applications.
On the other hand,
Defense Booster
is a useful skill tree.
Instead of adding an ability,
it increases defense.
Beginner Swordsmanship's
good too.
When maxed out, it can evolve
into the Advanced Swordsmanship
tree with special items.
[chuckles softly]
That said...
[gasps]
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Oath of the Heavy Armor
has reached Level Two.
Rampart Reflection skill
has been acquired.
Oath of the Heavy Armor
has reached Level Five.
Defense has increased by 10.
[ELYMAS] All right.
[grunts] That'll work.
[birds chirping]
♪
[cape rustling]
[gasps]
- [leaves rustling]
- [birds chirping]
[leaves rustling]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
- [croaks]
- [gasps]
[croaking]
A Raana? Display stats.
- [Raana croaks]
- [gasps]
[ELYMAS] You don't waste time.
Bring it!
- [Raana croaks]
- [grunts]
Rampart Reflection!
[groans]
[cape rustling]
[sighs]
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Level Two has been reached.
[ELYMAS] Well.
I had no idea
it would be this disgusting.
[AUTOMATED VOICE] When an enemy
melee attack is negated,
deal damage equal
to the user's Defense.
[birds chirping]
[ELYMAS]
A Level Two Magic Stone.
It's not worth much,
but I'll take it.
- [man yelling in panic]
- [gasps]
[MAN] Someone. Help me, please!
[gasps, grunts]
[yells]
[yelling]
They're gonna kill me!
- Who are you?
- [gasps]
Please. You have to help me!
- Huh?
- [Raanas croaking]
- [yells]
- [Elymas gasps]
[croaking]
[screams]
- [croaking]
- [man gasps]
[whimpering]
- Stand back.
- Huh?
Ah!
Can you really take them down?
[gasps] Even though
you don't look the part,
are you actually
a famous adventurer?
[ELYMAS] No.
Huh?!
In fact, I just leveled up
for the first time
in my whole life.
So you're hopeless?!
Stop! Come back!
You're too weak!
I'm much stronger than you
and I can't handle
that many monsters!
Now take off that heavy armor!
We have to run!
[ELYMAS] Rampart Reflection
isn't perfect.
My defense needs to be greater
than my opponent's attack
to negate all damage.
If my defense is lower,
then it won't even activate.
Run away!
- [croaks]
- [squeals]
[ELYMAS] It's useless against
superior and unknown foes.
- [croaking]
- But still...
Let's go. Rampart Reflection!
[grunts]
Huh?
[ELYMAS] I'm already familiar
with these starter enemies.
And I've boosted my defense
with skill tree bonuses
and equipment.
When it comes to Raana,
I can beat dozens of them.
No problem!
- [grunts]
- [Raanas groaning]
[gasps in disbelief]
[cape rustling]
[splutters]
You brought down that many?
Wait. Who are you?
The name's Elymas Ed--
If you ever use
the Edvaughn family name
outside of these walls,
I'll have your head
for such insolence!
I'm so sorry.
[huffs irritably]
[gasps] Hmm?
[ELYMAS] No.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
The Heavy Knight,
Elymas.
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[ELYMAS] I've won my very first
battle after being assigned
the Heavy Knight class.
And fortunately for me,
just like in the VR game,
it's still
the most powerful one.
But I still need to level up
to reach my full potential.
I don't have any time
to waste out here.
But at the moment,
a horrible monster
appears before me
that's double my level.
Next time, "The Menacing
Foul Eight-Legged Beast."
This battle isn't unwinnable!